<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

eu	ORG	ORG

rejects	O	O

german	MISC	MISC

call	O	O

to	O	O

boycott	O	O

british	MISC	MISC

lamb	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

peter	PER	PER

blackburn	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

brussels	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

on	O	O

it	O	O

to	O	O

until	O	O

scientists	O	O

disease	O	O

can	O	O

be	O	O

transmitted	O	O

to	O	O

sheep	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

union	ORG	ORG

werner	PER	PER

on	O	O

should	O	O

buy	O	O

from	O	O

other	O	O

than	O	O

the	O	O

scientific	O	O

advice	O	O

was	O	O

clearer	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

we	O	O

we	O	O

any	O	O

for	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

the	O	O

's	O	O

chief	O	O

nikolaus	PER	PER

van	PER	PER

der	PER	PER

pas	PER	ORG

told	O	O

a	O	O

news	O	O

briefing	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

he	O	O

and	O	O

found	O	O

that	O	O

was	O	O

it	O	O

should	O	O

be	O	O

taken	O	O

by	O	O

the	O	O

european	ORG	ORG

union	ORG	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

he	O	O

said	O	O

proposal	O	O

eu	ORG	ORG

farm	O	O

franz	PER	PER

ban	O	O

,	O	O

spleens	O	O

the	O	O

and	O	O

a	O	O

and	O	O

move	O	O

to	O	O

protect	O	O

human	O	ORG

health	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

measures	O	O

from	O	O

britain	LOC	LOC

france	LOC	LOC

under	O	O

encephalopathy	MISC	O

(	O	O

bse	MISC	MISC

)	O	O

--	O	O

mad	O	O

cow	O	O

disease	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

but	O	O

his	O	O

proposal	O	O

's	O	O

standing	O	O

,	O	O

health	O	O

,	O	O

if	O	O

as	O	O

there	O	O

only	O	O

a	O	O

slight	O	O

risk	O	O

to	O	O

human	O	O

health	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

de	PER	PER

palacio	PER	PER

an	O	O

eu	ORG	ORG

'	O	O

of	O	O

through	O	O

"	O	O

dangerous	O	O

generalisation	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

and	O	O

britain	LOC	LOC

backed	O	O

fischler	PER	PER

's	O	O

proposal	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

eu	ORG	ORG

are	O	O

the	O	O

early	O	O

next	O	O

make	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

senior	O	O

veterinary	O	O

officials	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

been	O	O

scrapie	O	O

,	O	O

a	O	O

to	O	O

is	O	O

believed	O	O

to	O	O

have	O	O

to	O	O

feed	O	O

containing	O	O

animal	O	O

waste	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

british	MISC	MISC

on	O	O

there	O	O

was	O	O

any	O	O

to	O	O

human	O	O

health	O	O

,	O	O

but	O	O

influence	O	O

consumers	O	O

across	O	O

europe	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

what	O	O

have	O	O

be	O	O

of	O	O

is	O	O

other	O	O

to	O	O

lead	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

'	ORG	O

union	ORG	O

(	O	O

nfu	ORG	ORG

)	O	O

chairman	O	O

john	PER	PER

lloyd	PER	PER

jones	PER	PER

said	O	O

on	O	O

bbc	ORG	ORG

radio	ORG	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

led	O	O

to	O	O

health	O	O

march	O	O

a	O	O

report	O	O

an	O	O

to	O	O

by	O	O

eating	O	O

contaminated	O	O

beef	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

47,600	O	O

from	O	O

britain	LOC	LOC

last	O	O

year	O	O

,	O	O

nearly	O	O

half	O	O

of	O	O

total	O	O

imports	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

it	O	O

4,275	O	O

of	O	O

,	O	O

some	O	O

10	O	O

percent	O	O

of	O	O

overall	O	O

imports	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

hendrix	PER	PER

song	O	O

draft	O	O

sells	O	O

for	O	O

almost	O	O

$	O	O

17,000	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

a	O	O

early	O	O

of	O	O

a	O	O

song	O	O

by	O	O

u.s.	LOC	LOC

guitar	O	O

jimi	PER	PER

was	O	O

almost	O	O

$	O	O

17,000	O	O

on	O	O

at	O	O

some	O	O

of	O	O

late	O	O

musician	O	O

's	O	O

favourite	O	O

possessions	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

a	O	O

paid	O	O

10,925	O	O

(	O	O

$	O	O

16,935	O	O

)	O	O

of	O	O

"	O	O

ai	MISC	PER

n't	MISC	O

no	MISC	O

"	O	O

,	O	O

a	O	O

of	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

hotel	O	O

stationery	O	O

in	O	O

late	O	O

1966	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

end	O	O

a	O	O

1967	O	O

in	O	O

he	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

,	O	O

where	O	O

it	O	O

was	O	O

retrieved	O	O

by	O	O

a	O	O

fan	O	O

.	O	O

<s>	O	O

also	O	O

up	O	O

16	O	O

items	O	O

were	O	O

put	O	O

former	O	O

etchingham	PER	PER

,	O	O

who	O	O

lived	O	O

with	O	O

him	O	O

from	O	O

1966	O	O

to	O	O

1969	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

mother	O	O

of	O	O

used	O	O

,	O	O

an	O	O

purchaser	O	O

bought	O	O

for	O	O

5,060	O	O

pounds	O	O

(	O	O

$	O	O

7,845	O	O

)	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

guitarist	O	O

died	O	O

of	O	O

a	O	O

drugs	O	O

overdose	O	O

in	O	O

1970	O	O

aged	O	O

27	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

says	O	O

taiwan	LOC	LOC

spoils	O	O

atmosphere	O	O

for	O	O

talks	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

beijing	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

on	O	O

accused	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

a	O	O

of	O	O

talks	O	O

a	O	O

visit	O	O

to	O	O

by	O	O

vice	O	O

chan	PER	PER

this	O	O

week	O	O

that	O	O

infuriated	O	O

beijing	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

hours	O	O

right	O	O

to	O	O

in	O	O

with	O	O

,	O	O

shen	PER	PER

guofang	PER	PER

told	O	O

reuters	ORG	ORG

:	O	O

"	O	O

the	O	O

of	O	O

by	O	O

the	O	O

taiwan	LOC	LOC

authorities	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

's	O	O

with	O	O

,	O	O

tang	PER	PER

,	O	O

telling	O	O

a	O	O

on	O	O

time	O	O

the	O	O

rivals	O	O

to	O	O

hold	O	O

political	O	O

talks	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

"	O	O

is	O	O

time	O	O

two	O	O

sides	O	O

to	O	O

engage	O	O

in	O	O

political	O	O

talks	O	O

...	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

that	O	O

is	O	O

to	O	O

state	O	O

of	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

people	ORG	O

's	ORG	ORG

daily	ORG	O

quoted	O	O

tang	PER	PER

as	O	O

saying	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

's	O	O

told	O	O

reuters	ORG	ORG

television	ORG	O

in	O	O

an	O	O

he	O	O

had	O	O

read	O	O

reports	O	O

of	O	O

tang	PER	PER

gave	O	O

no	O	O

details	O	O

of	O	O

right	O	O

for	O	O

with	O	O

,	O	O

beijing	LOC	LOC

considers	O	O

a	O	O

renegade	O	O

province	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

which	O	O

long	O	O

taipei	LOC	LOC

gain	O	O

,	O	O

was	O	O

a	O	O

visit	O	O

to	O	O

this	O	O

week	O	O

by	O	O

taiwanese	MISC	ORG

vice	O	O

president	O	O

lien	PER	PER

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

says	O	O

time	O	O

right	O	O

for	O	O

taiwan	LOC	LOC

talks	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

beijing	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

said	O	O

time	O	O

with	O	O

and	O	O

practical	O	O

steps	O	O

towards	O	O

that	O	O

goal	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

be	O	O

to	O	O

and	O	O

of	O	O

,	O	O

xinhua	ORG	ORG

tang	PER	PER

,	O	O

chairman	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

straits	ORG	O

,	O	O

as	O	O

saying	O	O

late	O	O

on	O	O

wednesday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

july	O	O

car	O	O

registrations	O	O

up	O	O

14.2	O	O

pct	O	O

yr	O	O

/	O	O

yr	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

frankfurt	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

of	O	O

jumped	O	O

14.2	O	O

in	O	O

july	O	O

year	O	O

,	O	O

for	ORG	O

motor	ORG	O

vehicles	ORG	O

said	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

356,725	O	ORG

were	O	O

in	O	O

july	O	O

1996	O	O

--	O	O

304,850	O	ORG

passenger	O	O

cars	O	O

and	O	O

15,613	O	O

trucks	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

13.6	O	O

cars	O	O

and	O	O

2.2	O	O

percent	O	O

decline	O	O

for	O	O

trucks	O	O

from	O	O

july	O	O

1995	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

rose	O	O

32.7	O	O

percent	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

period	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

of	O	O

abroad	O	O

,	O	O

while	O	O

said	O	O

demand	O	O

was	O	O

weak	O	O

,	O	O

the	O	O

federal	O	O

office	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

car	O	O

posted	O	O

gains	O	O

in	O	O

registration	O	O

numbers	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

period	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

ag	ORG	ORG

won	O	O

77,719	O	O

,	O	O

slightly	O	O

more	O	O

than	O	O

a	O	O

quarter	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

total	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

ag	ORG	ORG

general	ORG	O

motors	ORG	ORG

came	O	O

in	O	O

with	O	O

49,269	O	O

,	O	O

16.4	O	O

percent	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

overall	O	O

figure	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

third	O	O

was	O	O

ford	ORG	O

with	O	O

35,563	O	O

registrations	O	O

,	O	O

or	O	O

11.7	O	O

percent	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

fewer	O	O

in	O	O

july	O	O

1996	O	O

compared	O	O

to	O	O

last	O	O

year	O	O

's	O	O

july	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

3,420	O	O

with	O	O

5522	O	O

registrations	O	O

in	O	O

july	O	O

a	O	O

year	O	O

earlier	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

porsche	ORG	ORG

's	O	O

registrations	O	O

fell	O	O

to	O	O

554	O	O

from	O	O

643	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

socialists	O	O

give	O	O

green	O	O

light	O	O

to	O	O

pm	O	O

for	O	O

elections	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

athens	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

socialist	O	ORG

gave	O	O

costas	PER	PER

to	O	O

call	O	O

,	O	O

costas	PER	PER

skandalidis	PER	PER

told	O	O

reporters	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

costas	PER	PER

make	O	O

an	O	O

a	O	O

cabinet	O	O

later	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

,	O	O

said	O	O

skandalidis	PER	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

--	O	O

dimitris	PER	PER

kontogiannis	PER	PER

,	O	O

athens	ORG	LOC

newsroom	ORG	ORG

+301	O	O

3311812-4	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

bayervb	ORG	ORG

sets	O	O

c$	MISC	MISC

100	O	O

million	O	O

six-year	O	O

bond	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

bond	O	O

was	O	O

by	O	O

lead	O	O

manager	O	O

toronto	PER	PER

dominion	PER	PER

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

borrower	O	O

bayerische	ORG	ORG

vereinsbank	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

amt	O	O

c$	MISC	MISC

100	O	O

mln	O	O

coupon	O	O

6.625	O	O

maturity	O	O

24.sep.02	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

type	O	O

straight	O	O

iss	O	O

price	O	O

100.92	O	O

pay	O	O

date	O	O

24.sep.96	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

full	O	O

fees	O	O

1.875	O	O

reoffer	O	O

99.32	O	O

spread	O	O

+20	O	O

bp	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

moody	O	ORG

aa1	O	ORG

listing	O	O

lux	O	O

pay	O	O

freq	O	O

=	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

s&p	ORG	ORG

=	O	O

denoms	O	PER

(	O	O

k	O	O

)	O	O

1-10-100	O	O

sale	O	O

limits	O	O

us	LOC	LOC

/	O	O

uk	LOC	LOC

/	O	O

ca	LOC	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

neg	O	ORG

plg	O	O

no	O	O

crs	O	O

deflt	O	O

no	O	O

force	O	O

maj	O	O

=	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

law	O	O

german	MISC	MISC

home	O	O

ctry	O	O

=	O	O

tax	O	O

provs	O	O

standard	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

mgt	O	O

/	O	O

und	O	O

0.275	O	O

sell	O	O

conc	O	O

1.60	O	O

praecip	O	O

=	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

underlying	O	O

govt	O	O

bond	O	O

7.0	O	O

pct	O	O

sept	O	O

2001	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

vereinsbank	ORG	ORG

is	O	O

joint	O	O

lead	O	O

manager	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

london	ORG	LOC

newsroom	ORG	ORG

+44	O	O

171	O	O

542	O	O

7658	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

venantius	ORG	ORG

sets	O	O

$	O	O

300	O	O

million	O	O

january	O	O

1999	O	O

frn	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

was	O	O

by	O	O

lehman	ORG	ORG

brothers	ORG	ORG

international	ORG	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

swedish	MISC	MISC

national	O	O

mortgage	O	O

agency	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

amt	O	O

$	O	O

300	O	O

mln	O	O

spread	O	O

-	O	O

12.5	O	O

bp	O	O

maturity	O	O

21.jan.99	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

type	O	O

frn	O	O

base	O	O

3m	ORG	ORG

libor	O	O

pay	O	O

date	O	O

s23.sep.96	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

last	O	O

moody	O	ORG

aa3	O	ORG

iss	O	ORG

price	O	O

99.956	O	O

full	O	O

fees	O	O

10	O	O

bp	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

last	O	O

s&p	ORG	ORG

aa+	O	O

reoffer	O	O

=	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

notes	O	O

s	O	O

short	O	O

first	O	O

coupon	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

denoms	O	O

(	O	O

k	O	O

)	O	O

1-10-100	O	O

sale	O	O

limits	O	O

us	LOC	LOC

/	O	O

uk	LOC	LOC

/	O	O

jp	LOC	LOC

/	O	O

fr	LOC	LOC

</s>	O	O

neg	O	ORG

plg	O	O

yes	O	O

crs	O	O

deflt	O	O

no	O	O

force	O	O

maj	O	O

ipma	O	O

2	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

law	O	O

home	O	O

ctry	O	O

sweden	LOC	LOC

tax	O	O

provs	O	O

standard	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

mgt	O	O

/	O	O

und	O	O

5	O	O

bp	O	O

sell	O	O

conc	O	O

5	O	O

bp	O	O

praecip	O	O

=	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

notes	O	O

issued	O	O

off	O	O

emtn	O	O

programme	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

london	ORG	LOC

newsroom	ORG	ORG

+44	O	O

171	O	O

542	O	O

8863	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

port	O	O

update	O	O

-	O	O

syria	LOC	LOC

-	O	O

lloyds	ORG	ORG

shipping	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

port	O	O

lloyds	ORG	ORG

shipping	ORG	ORG

intelligence	ORG	ORG

service	ORG	O

--	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

10	O	O

-	O	O

time	O	O

and	O	O

tartous	LOC	O

presently	O	O

24	O	O

hours	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

israel	LOC	LOC

plays	O	O

down	O	O

fears	O	O

of	O	O

war	O	O

with	O	O

syria	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

colleen	PER	PER

siegel	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

jerusalem	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

's	O	O

with	O	O

on	O	O

current	O	O

appeared	O	O

to	O	O

be	O	O

a	O	O

storm	O	O

in	O	O

a	O	O

teacup	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

who	O	O

as	O	O

's	O	O

with	O	O

,	O	O

israel	ORG	LOC

it	O	O

wanted	O	O

to	O	O

talk	O	O

rather	O	O

than	O	O

fight	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

me	O	O

the	O	O

priority	O	O

is	O	O

still	O	O

to	O	O

negotiate	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

,	O	O

,	O	O

assessment	O	O

in	O	O

is	O	O

that	O	O

is	O	O

essentially	O	O

a	O	O

storm	O	O

in	O	O

a	O	O

teacup	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

he	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

is	O	O

winding	O	O

up	O	O

his	O	O

term	O	O

as	O	O

ambassador	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

be	O	O

by	O	O

,	O	O

to	O	O

right-wing	O	O

likud	ORG	ORG

party	O	O

politician	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

israel	LOC	LOC

on	O	O

a	O	O

,	O	O

via	O	O

,	O	O

and	O	O

negotiations	O	O

without	O	O

preconditions	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

but	O	O

it	O	O

for	O	O

what	O	O

it	O	O

called	O	O

a	O	O

dangerous	O	O

atmosphere	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

israel	LOC	LOC

on	O	O

launching	O	O

it	O	O

that	O	O

had	O	O

recently	O	O

test	O	O

fired	O	O

a	O	O

missile	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

it	O	O

said	O	O

were	O	O

for	O	O

defensive	O	O

purposes	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

the	O	O

that	O	O

we	O	O

(	O	O

al-	PER	O

)	O	O

is	O	O

is	O	O

at	O	O

any	O	O

without	O	O

to	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

david	PER	PER

levy	PER	PER

told	O	O

israel	ORG	LOC

radio	ORG	O

in	O	O

an	O	O

interview	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

has	O	O

in	O	O

retain	O	O

golan	LOC	LOC

from	O	O

syria	LOC	LOC

in	O	O

the	O	O

1967	O	O

middle	LOC	LOC

east	LOC	LOC

war	O	O

.	O	O

<s>	O	O

have	O	O

over	O	O

golan	LOC	LOC

1991	O	O

the	O	O

's	O	O

willingness	O	O

to	O	O

make	O	O

golan	LOC	LOC

concessions	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

two	O	O

sides	O	O

were	O	O

last	O	O

held	O	O

in	O	O

february	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

out	O	O

of	O	O

damascus	LOC	LOC

are	O	O

bad	O	O

,	O	O

not	O	O

good	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

media	O	O

...	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

declarations	O	O

that	O	O

must	O	O

be	O	O

worrying	O	O

...	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

is	O	O

very	O	O

those	O	O

it	O	O

could	O	O

become	O	O

its	O	O

prisoners	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

levy	PER	PER

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

from	O	O

,	O	O

if	O	O

is	O	O

,	O	O

will	O	O

's	O	O

to	O	O

because	O	O

that	O	O

is	O	O

our	O	O

goal	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

he	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

we	O	O

do	O	O

not	O	O

want	O	O

a	O	O

war	O	O

,	O	O

god	PER	PER

forbid	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

no	O	O

one	O	O

benefits	O	O

from	O	O

wars	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

's	O	O

two	ORG	O

television	O	O

said	O	O

had	O	O

sent	O	O

a	O	O

"	O	O

calming	O	O

signal	O	O

"	O	O

to	O	O

israel	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

it	O	O

gave	O	O

no	O	O

source	O	O

for	O	O

the	O	O

report	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

and	O	O

's	O	O

said	O	O

they	O	O

could	O	O

not	O	O

confirm	O	O

it	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

television	O	O

also	O	O

said	O	O

reassure	O	O

via	O	O

cairo	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

the	O	O

united	LOC	LOC

states	LOC	LOC

and	O	O

moscow	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

diplomat	O	O

denies	O	O

nurses	O	O

stranded	O	O

in	O	O

libya	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

tunis	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

a	O	O

on	O	O

a	O	O

polish	MISC	MISC

this	O	O

that	O	O

visas	O	O

100	O	O

working	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

north	MISC	O

african	MISC	MISC

country	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

this	O	O

is	O	O

not	O	O

true	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

to	O	O

,	O	O

no	O	O

of	O	O

without	O	O

her	O	O

will	O	O

,	O	O

have	O	O

any	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

the	O	O

's	O	O

d'affaires	O	O

,	O	O

,	O	O

told	O	O

reuters	ORG	ORG

by	O	O

telephone	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

poland	LOC	LOC

's	O	O

said	O	O

this	O	O

team	O	O

to	O	O

,	O	O

but	O	O

the	O	O

was	O	O

work	O	O

such	O	O

as	O	O

non-payment	O	O

of	O	O

their	O	O

salaries	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

he	O	O

said	O	O

are	O	O

800	O	O

polish	MISC	MISC

nurses	O	O

working	O	O

in	O	O

libya	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

two	O	O

opposition	O	O

leaders	O	O

meet	O	O

in	O	O

baghdad	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

hassan	PER	PER

hafidh	PER	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

baghdad	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

an	O	O

on	O	O

to	O	O

support	O	O

to	O	O

's	O	O

iranian	MISC	MISC

troops	O	O

deep	O	O

inside	O	O

iraq	LOC	LOC

last	O	O

month	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

said	O	O

of	O	O

of	ORG	O

(	O	O

)	O	O

on	O	O

his	O	O

support	O	O

to	O	O

iran	LOC	LOC

's	O	O

rebel	O	O

kurds	MISC	MISC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

iranian	MISC	MISC

stand	O	O

by	O	O

with	O	O

the	O	O

resistance	O	ORG

movement	O	O

in	O	O

iranian	LOC	MISC

kurdistan	LOC	ORG

,	O	O

"	O	O

it	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

a	O	O

the	O	O

"	O	O

signals	O	O

a	O	O

level	O	O

of	O	O

and	O	O

the	O	O

iranian	MISC	MISC

kurdish	MISC	MISC

oppositions	O	O

"	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

iran	LOC	LOC

in	O	O

july	O	O

in	O	O

control	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

government	O	O

in	O	O

baghdad	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

iran	LOC	LOC

under	O	O

of	O	O

of	O	O

patriotic	ORG	ORG

union	ORG	ORG

of	ORG	O

kurdistan	ORG	ORG

(	O	O

puk	ORG	ORG

)	O	O

group	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

puk	ORG	ORG

's	O	O

(	O	O

kdp	ORG	ORG

)	O	O

,	O	O

have	O	O

under	O	O

control	O	O

were	O	O

ousted	O	O

from	O	O

kuwait	LOC	LOC

in	O	O

the	O	O

1991	O	O

gulf	MISC	MISC

war	MISC	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

most	O	O

a	O	O

u.s.-sponsored	MISC	O

ceasefire	O	O

last	O	O

year	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

had	O	O

been	O	O

in	O	O

near	O	O

iranian	MISC	MISC

border	O	O

over	O	O

the	O	O

last	O	O

two	O	O

days	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

it	O	O

100	O	O

kurds	MISC	MISC

were	O	O

killed	O	O

or	O	O

wounded	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

attack	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

iran	LOC	LOC

and	O	O

mount	O	O

and	O	O

at	O	O

in	O	O

pursuit	O	O

of	O	O

their	O	O

own	O	O

kurdish	MISC	MISC

rebels	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

air	O	O

force	O	O

in	O	O

from	O	O

possible	O	O

attacks	O	O

by	O	O

baghdad	LOC	LOC

troops	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

rates	O	O

steady	O	O

in	O	O

quiet	O	O

summer	O	O

trade	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

manama	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

this	O	O

week	O	O

trade	O	O

,	O	O

dealers	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

kingdom	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

there	O	O

were	O	O

no	O	O

changes	O	O

in	O	O

saudi	MISC	LOC

riyal	O	O

rates	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

market	O	O

was	O	O

very	O	O

of	O	O

summer	O	O

holidays	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

one	O	O

dealer	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

spot	O	O

riyal	O	PER

was	O	O

put	O	O

at	O	O

3.7504	O	O

/	O	O

06	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

dollar	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

one-month	MISC	O

at	O	O

5-1/2	O	O

,	O	O

3/8	O	O

,	O	O

three	O	O

were	O	O

5-5/8	O	O

,	O	O

1/2	O	O

percent	O	O

and	O	O

six	O	O

months	O	O

were	O	O

5-3/4	O	O

,	O	O

5/8	O	O

percent	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

one-year	MISC	ORG

funds	O	O

were	O	O

at	O	O

six	O	O

,	O	O

5-7/8	O	O

percent	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

approves	O	O

arafat	PER	PER

's	O	O

flight	O	O

to	O	O

west	LOC	LOC

bank	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

jerusalem	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

israel	LOC	LOC

gave	O	O

arafat	PER	PER

on	O	O

its	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

bank	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

a	O	O

crisis	O	O

,	O	O

an	O	O

arafat	PER	PER

adviser	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

the	O	O

problem	O	O

is	O	O

over	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

's	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

is	O	O

not	O	O

to	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

before	O	O

monday	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

nabil	PER	PER

abu	PER	PER

rdainah	PER	PER

told	O	O

reuters	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

arafat	PER	PER

been	O	O

scheduled	O	O

meet	O	O

peres	PER	PER

in	O	O

the	O	O

bank	LOC	LOC

on	O	O

was	O	O

to	O	O

israel	LOC	LOC

clearance	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

palestinian	MISC	MISC

leader	O	O

's	O	O

helicopters	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

accused	O	O

of	O	O

meeting	O	O

by	O	O

keeping	O	O

arafat	PER	PER

grounded	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

and	O	O

,	O	O

on	O	O

,	O	O

the	O	O

allenby	LOC	LOC

between	O	O

jordan	LOC	LOC

and	O	O

the	O	O

west	LOC	LOC

bank	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

arafat	PER	PER

decided	O	O

against	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

bank	LOC	LOC

on	O	O

,	O	O

israel	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

he	O	O

had	O	O

a	O	O

in	O	O

and	O	O

would	O	O

not	O	O

be	O	O

free	O	O

until	O	O

monday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

arafat	PER	PER

meet	O	O

peres	PER	PER

in	O	O

gaza	LOC	LOC

after	O	O

flight	O	O

ban	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

jerusalem	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

will	O	O

meet	O	O

peres	PER	PER

in	O	O

on	O	O

had	O	O

the	O	O

leader	O	O

from	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

for	O	O

talks	O	O

with	O	O

the	O	O

former	O	O

prime	O	O

minister	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

the	O	O

peres	PER	PER

at	O	O

erez	LOC	O

in	O	O

in	O	O

ramallah	LOC	LOC

as	O	O

planned	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

peres	PER	PER

'	O	O

office	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

had	O	O

a	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

bank	LOC	LOC

in	O	O

an	O	O

attempt	O	O

to	O	O

bar	O	O

the	O	O

meeting	O	O

with	O	O

peres	PER	PER

.	O	O

<s>	O	O

leader	O	O

peres	PER	PER

,	O	O

he	O	O

may	O	O

,	O	O

of	O	O

to	O	O

his	O	O

's	O	O

authority	O	O

to	O	O

conduct	O	O

peace	O	O

talks	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

embassy	O	O

says	O	O

taleban	MISC	MISC

guards	O	O

going	O	O

home	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

hilary	PER	PER

gush	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

dubai	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

afghan	MISC	MISC

guards	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

week	O	O

who	O	O

escaped	O	O

will	O	O

in	O	O

a	O	O

days	O	O

,	O	O

afghan	MISC	MISC

embassy	O	O

in	O	O

abu	LOC	LOC

dhabi	LOC	LOC

said	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

is	O	O

touch	O	O

with	O	O

the	O	O

uae	LOC	LOC

foreign	O	O

ministry	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

three	O	O

days	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

an	O	O

embassy	O	O

official	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

the	O	O

embassy	O	O

them	O	O

for	O	O

their	O	O

return	O	O

to	O	O

their	O	O

homeland	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

is	O	O

no	O	O

objection	O	O

to	O	O

their	O	O

travel	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

he	O	O

added	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

guards	O	O

were	O	O

russian	MISC	MISC

aircrew	O	O

who	O	O

to	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

of	O	O

in	O	O

kandahar	LOC	LOC

in	O	O

southern	O	O

afghanistan	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

uae	LOC	LOC

on	O	O

monday	O	O

over	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

red	ORG	ORG

crescent	ORG	ORG

,	O	O

possibly	O	O

last	O	O

tuesday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

it	O	O

has	O	O

since	O	O

been	O	O

silent	O	O

on	O	O

the	O	O

issue	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

whether	O	O

three	O	O

back	O	O

to	O	O

,	O	O

the	O	O

embassy	O	O

said	O	O

:	O	O

"	O	O

has	O	O

not	O	O

been	O	O

decided	O	O

,	O	O

but	O	O

possibly	O	O

kandahar	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

is	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

opposition	O	O

taleban	MISC	PER

militia	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

is	O	O

controlled	O	O

's	O	O

,	O	O

taleban	MISC	ORG

is	O	O

fighting	O	O

to	O	O

overthrow	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

embassy	O	O

men	O	O

,	O	O

believed	O	O

to	O	O

be	O	O

in	O	O

their	O	O

20s	O	O

,	O	O

were	O	O

currently	O	O

in	O	O

abu	LOC	LOC

dhabi	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

he	O	O

did	O	O

not	O	O

elaborate	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

,	O	O

aerostan	ORG	ORG

firm	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

republic	O	O

of	O	O

,	O	O

a	O	O

their	O	O

cargo	O	O

plane	O	O

to	O	O

land	O	O

in	O	O

august	O	O

1995	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

taleban	MISC	ORG

said	O	O

shipment	O	O

of	O	O

from	O	O

was	O	O

of	O	O

support	O	O

for	O	O

rabbani	PER	PER

's	O	O

government	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

the	O	O

crew	O	O

's	O	O

nationality	O	O

was	O	O

coincidental	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

diplomatic	O	O

attempts	O	O

to	O	O

free	O	O

the	O	O

seven	O	O

failed	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

russians	MISC	MISC

,	O	O

who	O	O

--	O	O

two	O	O

--	O	O

while	O	O

on	O	O

76	MISC	ORG

,	O	O

uae	LOC	LOC

capital	O	O

abu	LOC	LOC

dhabi	LOC	LOC

for	O	O

home	O	O

on	O	O

sunday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

's	O	O

saddam	PER	PER

meets	O	O

russia	LOC	LOC

's	O	O

zhirinovsky	PER	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

baghdad	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

to	O	O

"	O	O

"	O	O

,	O	O

iraqi	MISC	MISC

newspapers	O	O

said	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

"	O	O

the	O	O

keenness	O	O

to	O	O

with	O	O

russia	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

"	O	O

the	O	O

papers	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

saddam	PER	PER

before	O	O

he	O	O

on	O	O

his	O	O

liberal	ORG	O

party	ORG	O

the	O	O

duma	ORG	O

(	O	O

)	O	O

"	O	O

calling	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

"	O	O

on	O	O

iraq	LOC	LOC

after	O	O

its	O	O

1990	O	O

invasion	O	O

of	O	O

kuwait	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

on	O	O

he	O	O

the	O	O

help	O	O

on	O	O

for	O	O

of	O	O

good	O	O

ties	O	O

with	O	O

baghdad	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

stand	O	O

is	O	O

firm	O	O

,	O	O

namely	O	O

on	O	O

(	O	O

the	O	O

)	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

on	O	O

trade	O	O

russia	LOC	LOC

and	O	O

iraq	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

"	O	O

he	O	O

told	O	O

reporters	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

zhirinovsky	PER	PER

visited	O	O

iraq	LOC	LOC

twice	O	O

in	O	O

1995	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

was	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

referendum	O	O

on	O	O

,	O	O

saddam	PER	PER

's	O	O

term	O	O

for	O	O

seven	O	O

more	O	O

years	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

press	O	O

digest	O	O

-	O	O

iraq	LOC	LOC

-	O	O

aug	O	O

22	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

baghdad	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

are	O	O

some	O	O

of	O	O

stories	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

official	O	O

iraqi	MISC	MISC

press	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

<s>	O	O

has	O	O

stories	O	O

and	O	O

does	O	O

not	O	O

vouch	O	O

for	O	O

their	O	O

accuracy	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

thawra	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

chairman	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

liberal	O	O

party	O	O

vladimir	PER	PER

zhirinovsky	PER	PER

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

turkish	MISC	MISC

says	O	O

turkey	LOC	LOC

in	O	O

fair	O	O

that	O	O

will	O	O

be	O	O

held	O	O

in	O	O

november	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

iraq	LOC	LOC

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

of	O	O

12	O	O

of	O	O

arrives	O	O

in	O	O

umm	LOC	LOC

qasr	LOC	LOC

port	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

gulf	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

press	O	O

digest	O	O

-	O	O

lebanon	LOC	LOC

-	O	O

aug	O	O

22	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

beirut	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

<s>	O	O

are	O	O

stories	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

beirut	LOC	LOC

press	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

<s>	O	O

has	O	O

stories	O	O

and	O	O

does	O	O

not	O	O

vouch	O	O

for	O	O

their	O	O

accuracy	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

an-nahar	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

is	O	O

hizbollah	ORG	O

and	O	O

the	O	O

government	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

:	O	O

israeli	MISC	MISC

threats	O	O

do	O	O

no	O	O

serve	O	O

peace	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

as-safir	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

speaker	O	O

:	O	O

for	O	O

war	O	O

against	O	O

syria	LOC	LOC

and	O	O

lebanon	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

parliamentary	O	O

battle	O	O

in	O	O

beirut	LOC	LOC

..	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

three	O	O

main	O	O

lists	O	O

have	O	O

been	O	O

prepared	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

al-anwar	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

of	O	O

--	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

mount	LOC	LOC

lebanon	LOC	LOC

elections	O	O

last	O	O

sunday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

ad-diyar	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

between	O	O

lebanon	LOC	LOC

and	O	O

pakistan	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

hariri	PER	PER

battle	O	O

with	O	O

an	O	O

incomplete	O	O

list	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

nida'a	ORG	ORG

al-watan	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

patriarch	O	O

over	O	O

the	O	O

violations	O	O

in	O	O

sunday	O	O

'	O	O

elections	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

cme	ORG	ORG

and	O	O

feeder	O	O

cattle	O	O

calls	O	O

range	O	O

mixed	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

chicago	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

cme	ORG	ORG

futures	O	O

from	O	O

0.200	O	O

cent	O	O

to	O	O

0.100	O	O

lower	O	O

,	O	O

livestock	O	O

analysts	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

strong	O	O

tone	O	O

to	O	O

markets	O	O

should	O	O

prompt	O	O

further	O	O

support	O	O

.	O	O

<s>	O	O

a	O	O

is	O	O

also	O	O

to	O	O

prompt	O	O

some	O	O

bull	O	O

spreading	O	O

,	O	O

analysts	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

trade	O	O

be	O	O

light	O	O

and	O	O

could	O	O

on	O	O

evening	O	O

up	O	O

ahead	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

report	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

also	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

cattle	O	O

traded	O	O

this	O	O

week	O	O

,	O	O

they	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

says	O	O

debt	O	O

buy	O	O

to	O	O

hit	O	O

q1	O	O

results	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

montgomery	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

ala	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

on	O	O

that	O	O

a	O	O

mean	O	O

an	O	O

of	O	O

$	O	O

1.2	O	O

million	O	O

in	O	O

its	O	O

fiscal	O	O

1997	O	O

first	O	O

quarter	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

said	O	O

that	O	O

,	O	O

which	O	O

1	O	O

,	O	O

$	O	O

30	O	O

its	O	O

outstanding	O	O

10-3/8	O	O

percent	O	O

senior	O	O

notes	O	O

due	O	O

2001	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

notes	O	O

were	O	O

bought	O	O

for	O	O

$	O	O

31.5	O	O

million	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

chief	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

reduce	O	O

the	O	O

's	O	O

average	O	O

interest	O	O

costs	O	O

future	O	O

cash	O	O

flows	O	O

and	O	O

earnings	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

research	O	O

alert	O	O

-	O	O

lehman	ORG	LOC

starts	O	O

snet	ORG	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

bath	PER	PER

new	ORG	O

england	ORG	LOC

with	O	O

an	O	O

outperform	O	O

rating	O	O

,	O	O

his	O	O

office	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

the	O	O

analyst	O	O

a	O	O

of	O	O

$	O	O

45	O	O

and	O	O

a	O	O

1996	O	O

of	O	O

$	O	O

3.09	O	O

per	O	O

share	O	O

,	O	O

his	O	O

office	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

the	O	O

analyst	O	O

an	O	O

1997	O	O

,	O	O

figure	O	O

was	O	O

not	O	O

immediately	O	O

available	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

--	O	O

southern	ORG	O

new	ORG	O

england	ORG	LOC

closed	O	O

at	O	O

38-1/2	O	O

wednesday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

e.	PER	PER

auchard	PER	PER

,	O	O

wall	ORG	LOC

street	ORG	LOC

bureau	ORG	O

,	O	O

212-859-1736	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

gateway	ORG	ORG

data	ORG	ORG

sciences	ORG	ORG

q2	O	O

net	O	O

rises	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

phoenix	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

of	O	O

consolidated	ORG	ORG

financial	ORG	ORG

data	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

in	O	O

thousands	O	O

,	O	O

except	O	O

per	O	O

share	O	O

data	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

six	O	O

months	O	O

ended	O	O

quarter	O	O

ended	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

jul	O	O

31	O	O

,	O	O

jul	O	O

31	O	O

,	O	O

jul	O	O

31	O	O

,	O	O

jul	O	O

31	O	O

,	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

1996	O	ORG

1995	O	O

1996	O	O

1995	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

income	O	O

statement	O	O

data	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

total	O	O

revenue	O	O

$	O	O

10,756	O	O

$	O	O

13,102	O	O

$	O	O

7,961	O	O

$	O	O

5,507	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

software	O	O

revenue	O	O

2,383	O	O

1,558	O	O

1,086	O	O

1,074	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

services	O	O

revenue	O	O

1,154	O	O

692	O	O

624	O	O

465	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

operating	O	O

income	O	O

906	O	O

962	O	O

599	O	O

515	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

net	O	O

income	O	O

821	O	O

512	O	O

565	O	O

301	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

earnings	O	O

per	O	O

share	O	O

0.31	O	O

0.34	O	O

0.19	O	O

0.20	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

jul	O	O

31	O	O

,	O	O

1996	O	PER

jan	O	O

31	O	O

,	O	O

1996	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

balance	O	O

sheet	O	O

data	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

working	O	O

capital	O	O

$	O	O

5,755	O	O

(	O	O

$	O	O

881	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

cash	O	O

and	O	O

cash	O	O

equivalents	O	O

2,386	O	O

93	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

total	O	O

assets	O	O

14,196	O	O

7,138	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

shareholders	O	O

'	O	O

equity	O	O

5,951	O	O

(	O	O

1,461	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

socialists	O	O

give	O	O

pm	O	O

green	O	O

light	O	O

for	O	O

election	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

athens	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

socialist	O	ORG

costas	PER	PER

if	O	O

to	O	O

call	O	O

,	O	O

told	O	O

reporters	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

costas	PER	PER

make	O	O

an	O	O

a	O	O

cabinet	O	O

later	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

,	O	O

said	O	O

skandalidis	PER	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

--	O	O

dimitris	PER	PER

kontogiannis	PER	PER

,	O	O

athens	ORG	LOC

newsroom	ORG	ORG

+301	O	O

3311812-4	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

press	O	O

digest	O	O

-	O	O

france	LOC	LOC

-	O	O

le	ORG	ORG

monde	ORG	ORG

aug	O	O

22	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

paris	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

stories	O	O

in	O	O

's	O	O

afternoon	O	O

daily	O	O

le	ORG	ORG

monde	ORG	ORG

,	O	O

dated	O	O

aug	O	O

23	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

front	O	O

page	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

's	O	O

are	O	O

as	O	O

enters	O	O

49th	O	O

day	O	O

paris	LOC	LOC

and	O	O

wednesday	O	O

rally	O	O

attracts	O	O

8,000	O	O

sympathisers	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

end	O	O

of	O	O

truce	O	O

after	O	O

last	O	O

night	O	O

's	O	O

attacks	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

business	O	O

pages	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

's	O	O

factories	O	O

,	O	O

undercut	O	O

by	O	O

and	O	O

failure	O	O

to	O	O

keep	O	O

abreast	O	O

of	O	O

trends	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

of	O	O

trade	O	O

france	ORG	LOC

are	O	O

in	O	O

social	O	O

unrest	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

next	O	O

few	O	O

weeks	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

paris	ORG	LOC

newsroom	ORG	ORG

+33	O	O

1	O	O

42	O	O

21	O	O

53	O	O

81	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

well	O	O

to	O	O

lift	O	O

heidrun	LOC	O

oil	O	O

output	O	O

-	O	O

statoil	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

oslo	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

three	O	O

water	O	O

on	O	O

be	O	O

over	O	O

next	O	O

month	O	O

,	O	O

oljeselskap	ORG	O

as	ORG	O

(	O	O

statoil	ORG	ORG

)	O	O

said	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

a	O	O

dip	O	O

30,000	O	O

per	O	O

(	O	O

bpd	O	O

)	O	O

in	O	O

output	O	O

to	O	O

220,000	O	O

,	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

company	O	O

's	O	O

status	ORG	O

weekly	ORG	O

newsletter	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

be	O	O

and	O	O

will	O	O

be	O	O

the	O	O

reservoir	O	O

of	O	O

plugging	O	O

problems	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

future	O	O

,	O	O

it	O	O

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

oslo	LOC	LOC

newsroom	O	ORG

+47	O	O

22	O	O

42	O	O

50	O	O

41	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

april	O	O

trade	O	O

surplus	O	O

3.8	O	O

billion	O	O

markka	O	O

-	O	O

ncb	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

helsinki	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

rose	O	O

to	O	O

3.83	O	O

from	O	O

3.43	O	O

march	O	O

,	O	O

(	O	O

ncb	ORG	ORG

)	O	O

said	O	O

in	O	O

a	O	O

statement	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

of	O	O

imports	O	O

fell	O	O

two	O	O

percent	O	O

,	O	O

ncb	ORG	ORG

said	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

trade	O	O

balance	O	O

(	O	O

million	O	O

markka	O	O

)	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

april	O	O

'	O	O

96	O	O

march	O	O

'	O	O

96	O	O

jan-april	O	O

'	O	O

96	O	O

jan-april	O	O

'	O	O

95	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

imports	O	O

10,663	O	O

10,725	O	O

43,430	O	O

40,989	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

exports	O	O

14,494	O	O

14,153	O	O

56,126	O	O

56,261	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

balance	O	O

+3,831	O	O

+3,428	O	O

+12,696	O	O

+15,272	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

1995	O	O

figure	O	O

39,584	O	O

the	O	O

export	O	O

figure	O	O

from	O	O

55,627	O	O

million	O	O

markka	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

bank	ORG	O

of	ORG	O

april	O	O

3.2	O	O

exports	O	O

at	O	O

14.5	O	O

billion	O	O

and	O	O

imports	O	O

at	O	O

11.3	O	O

billion	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

ncb	ORG	ORG

's	O	O

monthly	O	O

are	O	O

in	O	O

the	O	O

european	ORG	ORG

union	ORG	ORG

at	O	O

the	O	O

start	O	O

of	O	O

1995	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

helsinki	ORG	LOC

newsroom	ORG	ORG

+358	O	O

-	O	O

0	O	O

-	O	O

680	O	O

50	O	O

245	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

dutch	MISC	MISC

state	O	O

raises	O	O

tap	O	O

sale	O	O

price	O	O

to	O	O

99.95	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

amsterdam	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

the	O	O

for	O	O

of	O	O

dutch	MISC	MISC

5.75	O	O

percent	O	O

bond	O	O

due	O	O

september	O	O

2002	O	O

to	O	O

99.95	O	O

from	O	O

99.90	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

on	O	O

monday	O	O

are	O	O

from	O	O

07.00	O	O

gmt	MISC	MISC

to	O	O

15.00	O	O

gmt	MISC	MISC

until	O	O

further	O	O

notice	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

2.3	O	O

of	O	O

bond	O	O

by	O	O

the	O	O

close	O	O

of	O	O

trade	O	O

on	O	O

wednesday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

--	O	O

amsterdam	LOC	LOC

newsroom	O	O

+31	O	O

20	O	O

504	O	O

5000	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

tells	O	O

consumers	O	O

to	O	O

avoid	O	O

british	MISC	MISC

mutton	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

bonn	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

on	O	O

from	O	O

until	O	O

scientists	O	O

can	O	O

be	O	O

transmitted	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

animals	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

"	O	O

is	O	O

up	O	O

the	O	O

union	ORG	ORG

--	O	O

this	O	O

to	O	O

be	O	O

done	O	O

as	O	O

--	O	O

(	O	O

)	O	O

should	O	O

if	O	O

all	O	O

possible	O	O

to	O	O

other	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

werner	PER	PER

zwingmann	PER	PER

told	O	O

zdf	ORG	ORG

television	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

i	O	O

do	O	O

to	O	O

say	O	O

a	O	O

danger	O	O

for	O	O

consumers	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

he	O	O

added	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

too	O	O

in	O	O

what	O	O

,	O	O

and	O	O

these	O	O

must	O	O

be	O	O

filled	O	O

very	O	O

quickly	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

led	O	O

tops	O	O

list	O	O

of	O	O

with	O	O

crisis	O	O

,	O	O

which	O	O

march	O	O

a	O	O

illness	O	O

by	O	O

eating	O	O

contaminated	O	O

beef	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

rethink	O	O

proposal	O	O

questioned	O	O

whether	O	O

it	O	O

was	O	O

justified	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

eu	ORG	ORG

farm	O	O

franz	PER	PER

proposed	O	O

banning	O	O

,	O	O

spleens	O	O

the	O	O

and	O	O

from	O	O

britain	LOC	LOC

france	LOC	LOC

under	O	O

encephalopathy	MISC	O

(	O	O

bse	MISC	MISC

)	O	O

--	O	O

mad	O	O

cow	O	O

disease	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

but	O	O

some	O	O

of	O	O

's	O	O

standing	O	O

whether	O	O

was	O	O

given	O	O

the	O	O

slight	O	O

risk	O	O

to	O	O

human	O	O

health	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

is	O	O

being	O	O

by	O	O

two	O	O

eu	ORG	ORG

scientific	O	O

committees	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

been	O	O

scrapie	O	O

,	O	O

a	O	O

to	O	O

is	O	O

believed	O	O

to	O	O

have	O	O

to	O	O

feed	O	O

containing	O	O

animal	O	O

waste	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

british	MISC	MISC

sheep	O	O

meat	O	O

is	O	O

perfectly	O	O

safe	O	O

to	O	O

eat	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

zdf	ORG	ORG

said	O	O

47,600	O	O

from	O	O

britain	LOC	LOC

last	O	O

year	O	O

,	O	O

nearly	O	O

half	O	O

of	O	O

total	O	O

imports	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

it	O	O

4,275	O	O

of	O	O

,	O	O

some	O	O

10	O	O

percent	O	O

of	O	O

overall	O	O

imports	O	O

.	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

british	MISC	MISC

a	O	O

and	O	O

its	O	O

fatal	O	O

,	O	O

eu	ORG	ORG

a	O	O

worldwide	O	O

ban	O	O

on	O	O

british	MISC	MISC

beef	O	O

exports	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

eu	ORG	ORG

a	O	O

in	O	O

of	O	O

ban	O	O

britain	LOC	LOC

measures	O	O

to	O	O

eradicate	O	O

the	O	O

disease	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

golf	O	O

-	O	O

scores	O	O

at	O	O

world	MISC	MISC

series	MISC	O

of	MISC	O

golf	MISC	MISC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

akron	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

ohio	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scores	O	O

from	O	O

the	O	O

$	O	O

2.1	O	O

</s>	O	O

series	MISC	O

of	MISC	O

golf	MISC	O

after	O	O

the	O	O

first	O	O

round	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

at	O	O

the	O	O

7,149	O	ORG

yard	O	O

,	O	O

par	O	O

70	O	O

firestone	LOC	LOC

c.c	LOC	O

course	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

players	O	O

u.s.	LOC	LOC

unless	O	O

stated	O	O

)	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

66	O	O

,	O	O

mayfair	PER	PER

,	O	O

hidemichi	PER	PER

tanaka	PER	PER

(	O	O

japan	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

68	O	O

steve	PER	PER

stricker	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

69	O	O

justin	PER	PER

leonard	PER	PER

,	O	O

mark	PER	PER

brooks	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

70	O	O

,	O	O

,	O	O

davis	PER	PER

love	PER	PER

,	O	O

anders	PER	PER

forsbrand	PER	O

</s>	O	O

(	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

(	O	O

britain	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

,	O	O

john	PER	PER

cook	PER	PER

,	O	O

steve	PER	PER

jones	PER	PER

,	O	O

phil	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

mickelson	PER	PER

,	O	O

greg	PER	PER

norman	PER	PER

(	O	O

australia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

71	O	O

ernie	PER	PER

els	PER	PER

(	O	O

south	LOC	LOC

africa	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

,	O	O

scott	PER	PER

hoch	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

72	O	O

,	O	O

roberts	PER	PER

,	O	O

fred	PER	PER

funk	PER	PER

,	O	O

sven	PER	PER

struver	PER	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

cejka	PER	PER

(	O	O

germany	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

,	O	O

hal	PER	PER

sutton	PER	PER

,	O	O

tom	PER	PER

lehman	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

73	O	O

d.a.	PER	PER

,	O	O

brad	PER	PER

bryant	PER	PER

,	O	O

craig	PER	PER

parry	PER	PER

(	O	O

australia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

,	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

corey	PER	PER

pavin	PER	PER

,	O	O

craig	PER	PER

stadler	PER	PER

,	O	O

mark	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

o'meara	PER	PER

,	O	O

fred	PER	PER

couples	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

74	O	O

stankowski	PER	PER

,	O	O

costantino	PER	PER

rocca	PER	PER

(	O	O

italy	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

75	O	O

furyk	PER	PER

,	O	O

satoshi	PER	PER

higashi	PER	PER

(	O	O

japan	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

,	O	O

willie	PER	PER

wood	PER	PER

,	O	O

shigeki	PER	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

maruyama	PER	PER

(	O	O

japan	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

76	O	O

scott	PER	PER

mccarron	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

77	O	O

(	O	O

south	LOC	LOC

africa	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

,	O	O

steve	PER	PER

schneiter	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

79	O	O

tom	PER	PER

watson	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

81	O	ORG

seiki	PER	O

okuda	PER	PER

(	O	O

japan	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

gloria	ORG	ORG

bistrita	ORG	ORG

beat	O	O

2-1	O	O

f.c.	ORG	ORG

valletta	ORG	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

bistrita	LOC	ORG

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

gloria	ORG	ORG

(	O	O

)	O	O

beat	O	O

2-1	O	O

(	O	O

1-1	O	O

)	O	O

(	O	O

malta	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

in	O	O

cup	MISC	MISC

,	O	O

leg	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

preliminary	O	O

round	O	O

,	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scorers	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

gloria	ORG	ORG

-	O	O

ilie	PER	PER

lazar	PER	PER

(	O	O

32nd	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

eugen	PER	PER

voica	PER	PER

(	O	O

84th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

f.c.	ORG	ORG

la	ORG	ORG

valletta	ORG	LOC

-	O	O

gilbert	PER	PER

agius	PER	PER

(	O	O

24th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

8,000	O	O

</s>	O	O

gloria	ORG	ORG

4-2	O	O

and	O	O

the	O	O

first	O	O

round	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

cup	MISC	MISC

winners	MISC	MISC

cup	MISC	MISC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

reuter	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

ends	O	O

25-year	O	O

wait	O	O

for	O	O

trainer	O	O

prescott	PER	PER

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

york	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

england	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

his	O	O

25	O	O

his	O	O

,	O	O

a	O	O

100-30	O	O

,	O	O

won	O	O

the	O	O

nunthorpe	MISC	O

stakes	MISC	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

by	O	O

,	O	O

a	O	O

verdict	O	O

in	O	O

last	O	O

to	O	O

(	O	O

16-1	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

candy	PER	PER

and	O	O

ridden	O	O

by	O	O

chris	PER	PER

rutter	PER	PER

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

11-4	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

last	O	O

's	O	O

de	MISC	ORG

l	MISC	ORG

'	MISC	O

winner	O	O

,	O	O

,	O	O

a	O	O

further	O	O

and	O	O

lengths	O	O

with	O	O

the	O	O

7-4	O	O

favourite	O	O

mind	PER	PER

games	PER	PER

in	O	O

fourth	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

a	O	O

winner	O	O

in	O	O

,	O	O

be	O	O

at	O	O

this	O	O

's	O	O

abbaye	MISC	O

,	O	O

europe	LOC	LOC

's	O	O

top	O	O

sprint	O	O

race	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

to	O	O

winner	O	O

's	O	O

the	O	O

of	O	O

was	O	O

,	O	O

said	O	O

:	O	O

"	O	O

years	O	O

and	O	O

have	O	O

been	O	O

there	O	O

so	O	O

i	O	O

thought	O	O

i	O	O

had	O	O

better	O	O

wait	O	O

a	O	O

bit	O	O

longer	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

he	O	O

added	O	O

:	O	O

"	O	O

's	O	O

very	O	O

to	O	O

beat	O	O

i	O	O

am	O	O

godfather	O	O

to	O	O

his	O	O

daughter	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

jack	PER	PER

,	O	O

of	O	O

,	O	O

gone	O	O

's	O	O

in	O	O

of	O	O

a	O	O

years	O	O

around	O	O

the	O	O

top	O	O

of	O	O

his	O	O

profession	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

said	O	O

:	O	O

"	O	O

but	O	O

i	O	O

do	O	O

n't	O	O

feel	O	O

suicidal	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

he	O	O

(	O	O

games	PER	PER

)	O	O

as	O	O

well	O	O

as	O	O

of	O	O

them	O	O

a	O	O

(	O	O

300	O	O

metres	O	O

)	O	O

out	O	O

but	O	O

he	O	O

just	O	O

did	O	O

n't	O	O

quicken	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

horse	O	O

racing	O	O

-	O	O

nunthorpe	O	O

stakes	O	MISC

results	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

york	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

england	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

,	O	O

a	O	O

for	O	O

,	O	O

run	O	O

over	O	O

five	O	O

furlongs	O	O

(	O	O

1	O	O

km	O	O

)	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

1.	O	O

pivotal	PER	PER

100-30	O	PER

(	O	O

ridden	O	O

by	O	O

george	PER	PER

duffield	PER	PER

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

2.	O	ORG

eveningperformance	PER	O

16-1	O	O

(	O	O

chris	PER	PER

rutter	PER	PER

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

3.	O	O

hever	PER	PER

golf	PER	PER

rose	PER	O

11-4	O	O

(	O	O

jason	PER	PER

weaver	PER	PER

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

eight	O	O

ran	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

favourite	O	O

:	O	O

mind	PER	PER

games	PER	PER

(	O	O

7-4	O	O

)	O	O

finished	O	O

4th	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

distances	O	O

:	O	O

a	O	O

short	O	O

head	O	O

,	O	O

1-1/4	O	PER

lengths	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

owned	O	O

cheveley	ORG	ORG

park	ORG	ORG

stud	ORG	ORG

and	O	O

trained	O	O

by	O	O

sir	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

mark	PER	PER

prescott	PER	PER

at	O	O

newmarket	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

value	O	O

to	O	O

winner	O	O

:	O	O

72,464	O	ORG

pounds	O	O

sterling	O	O

(	O	O

$	O	O

112,200	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

tennis	O	O

-	O	O

results	O	O

at	O	O

toshiba	MISC	MISC

classic	MISC	MISC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

carlsbad	LOC	LOC

,	O	O

california	LOC	ORG

1996-08-21	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

results	O	O

from	O	O

the	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

$	O	O

450,000	O	O

toshiba	MISC	MISC

tennis	O	O

tournament	O	O

on	O	O

wednesday	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

prefix	O	O

number	O	O

denotes	O	O

seeding	O	O

)	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

second	O	O

round	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

1	O	O

-	O	O

vicario	PER	PER

(	O	O

spain	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

naoko	PER	PER

kijimuta	PER	PER

(	O	O

japan	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

1-6	O	O

6-4	O	O

6-3	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

4	O	O

-	O	O

kimiko	PER	PER

date	PER	PER

(	O	O

japan	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

yone	PER	PER

kamio	PER	O

(	O	O

japan	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-2	O	O

7-5	O	O

</s>	O	O

testud	PER	O

(	O	O

france	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

7	O	O

-	O	O

ai	PER	PER

sugiyama	PER	PER

(	O	O

japan	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-3	O	O

4-6	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

6-4	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

8	O	O

-	O	O

tauziat	PER	PER

(	O	O

france	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

shi-ting	PER	PER

wang	PER	PER

(	O	O

taiwan	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-4	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

6-2	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

tennis	O	O

-	O	O

results	O	O

at	O	O

hamlet	MISC	MISC

cup	MISC	MISC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

commack	LOC	ORG

,	O	O

new	LOC	LOC

york	LOC	LOC

1996-08-21	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

results	O	O

from	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

cup	MISC	MISC

tournament	O	O

on	O	O

wednesday	O	O

(	O	O

prefix	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

number	O	O

denotes	O	O

seeding	O	O

)	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

second	O	O

round	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

1	O	O

-	O	O

michael	PER	PER

chang	PER	PER

(	O	O

u.s.	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

sergi	PER	PER

bruguera	PER	O

(	O	O

spain	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-3	O	O

6-2	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

michael	PER	PER

joyce	PER	PER

(	O	O

u.s.	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

3	O	O

-	O	O

richey	PER	PER

reneberg	PER	PER

(	O	O

u.s.	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

3-6	O	O

6-4	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

6-3	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

damm	PER	PER

(	O	O

republic	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

6	O	O

-	O	O

younes	PER	PER

el	PER	PER

aynaoui	PER	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

morocco	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

5-7	O	O

6-3	O	O

3-0	O	O

retired	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

slovakia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

hicham	PER	PER

arazi	PER	O

(	O	O

morocco	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

7-6	O	O

(	O	O

7-4	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

7-5	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

dalglish	PER	PER

sad	O	O

over	O	O

blackburn	ORG	ORG

parting	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

on	O	O

of	O	O

his	O	O

at	O	O

,	O	O

the	O	O

he	O	O

led	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

english	MISC	MISC

premier	O	O

league	O	O

title	O	O

in	O	O

1994-95	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

on	O	O

and	O	O

had	O	O

parted	O	O

by	O	O

mutual	O	O

consent	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

on	O	O

to	O	O

being	O	O

"	O	O

"	O	O

at	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

title	O	O

inside	O	O

three	O	O

and	O	O

a	O	O

half	O	O

years	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

a	O	O

to	O	O

a	O	O

his	O	O

home	O	O

,	O	O

:	O	O

"	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

,	O	O

the	O	O

came	O	O

to	O	O

it	O	O

a	O	O

little	O	O

bit	O	O

earlier	O	O

than	O	O

me	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

he	O	O

:	O	O

"	O	O

if	O	O

no	O	O

one	O	O

asked	O	O

,	O	O

i	O	O

never	O	O

opened	O	O

my	O	O

mouth	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

way	O	O

and	O	O

let	O	O

them	O	O

get	O	O

on	O	O

with	O	O

the	O	O

job	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

the	O	O

thought	O	O

(	O	O

job	O	O

)	O	O

had	O	O

run	O	O

course	O	O

and	O	O

i	O	O

came	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

same	O	O

conclusion	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

with	O	O

years	O	O

,	O	O

as	O	O

,	O	O

the	O	O

past	O	O

15	O	O

months	O	O

,	O	O

as	O	O

director	O	O

of	O	O

football	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

cricket	O	O

-	O	O

english	MISC	MISC

county	MISC	O

championship	MISC	O

scores	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

close	O	O

of	O	O

play	O	O

scores	O	O

in	O	O

four-day	O	O

</s>	O	O

cricket	O	O

matches	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

second	O	O

day	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

at	O	O

weston-super-mare	LOC	LOC

:	O	O

durham	ORG	ORG

326	O	O

(	O	O

d.	PER	PER

cox	PER	PER

95	O	O

not	O	O

out	O	O

,	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

s.	PER	PER

campbell	PER	PER

69	O	O

;	O	O

g.	PER	PER

rose	PER	PER

7-73	O	O

)	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

somerset	ORG	ORG

236-4	O	O

(	O	O

m.	PER	PER

lathwell	PER	PER

85	O	O

)	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

firsy	O	MISC

day	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

:	O	O

gloucestershire	ORG	ORG

280	O	O

(	O	O

j.	PER	PER

russell	PER	PER

63	O	O

,	O	O

a.	PER	PER

symonds	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

52	O	O

;	O	O

a.	PER	PER

cowan	PER	PER

5-68	O	O

)	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

essex	ORG	ORG

72-0	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

at	O	O

:	O	O

kent	ORG	ORG

128-1	O	O

(	O	O

m.	PER	PER

walker	PER	PER

59	O	O

,	O	O

d.	PER	PER

fulton	PER	PER

53	O	O

not	O	O

out	O	O

)	O	O

v	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

glamorgan	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

at	O	O

:	O	O

leicestershire	ORG	ORG

343-8	O	O

(	O	O

p.	PER	PER

simmons	PER	PER

108	O	O

,	O	O

p.	PER	PER

nixon	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

67	O	O

not	O	O

out	O	O

)	O	O

v	O	O

hampshire	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

:	O	O

sussex	ORG	ORG

368-7	O	O

(	O	O

n.	PER	PER

lenham	PER	PER

145	O	O

,	O	O

v.	PER	PER

drakes	PER	PER

59	O	O

not	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

out	O	O

,	O	O

a.	PER	PER

wells	PER	PER

51	O	O

)	O	O

v	O	O

northamptonshire	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

at	O	O

trent	LOC	LOC

bridge	LOC	LOC

:	O	O

nottinghamshire	ORG	ORG

392-6	O	O

(	O	O

g.	PER	PER

archer	PER	PER

143	O	O

not	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

out	O	O

,	O	O

m.	PER	PER

dowman	PER	PER

107	O	O

)	O	O

v	O	O

surrey	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

at	O	O

:	O	O

warwickshire	ORG	ORG

255-9	O	O

(	O	O

a.	PER	PER

giles	PER	PER

57	O	O

not	O	O

out	O	O

,	O	O

w.	PER	PER

khan	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

52	O	O

)	O	O

v	O	O

worcestershire	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

at	O	O

:	O	O

yorkshire	ORG	ORG

305-5	O	O

(	O	O

c.	PER	PER

white	PER	PER

66	O	O

not	O	O

out	O	O

,	O	O

m.	PER	PER

moxon	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

66	O	ORG

,	O	O

m.	PER	PER

vaughan	PER	PER

57	O	O

)	O	O

v	O	O

lancashire	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

cricket	O	O

-	O	O

england	LOC	LOC

v	O	O

pakistan	LOC	LOC

final	O	O

test	O	O

scoreboard	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scoreboard	O	O

on	O	O

the	O	O

first	O	O

day	O	O

of	O	O

the	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

and	O	O

final	O	O

test	O	O

england	LOC	LOC

and	O	O

pakistan	LOC	LOC

at	O	O

the	LOC	LOC

oval	LOC	LOC

on	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

thursday	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

england	LOC	LOC

first	O	O

innings	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

m.	PER	PER

atherton	PER	PER

b	O	O

waqar	PER	PER

younis	PER	PER

31	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

a.	PER	PER

stewart	PER	PER

b	O	O

mushtaq	PER	PER

ahmed	PER	PER

44	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

n.	PER	PER

hussain	PER	PER

c	O	O

saeed	PER	PER

anwar	PER	PER

b	O	O

waqar	PER	PER

younis	PER	PER

12	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

g.	PER	PER

thorpe	PER	PER

lbw	O	O

b	O	O

mohammad	PER	PER

akram	PER	PER

54	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

j.	PER	PER

crawley	PER	PER

not	O	O

out	O	O

94	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

n.	PER	PER

knight	PER	PER

b	O	O

mushtaq	PER	PER

ahmed	PER	PER

17	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

c.	PER	PER

lewis	PER	PER

b	O	O

wasim	PER	PER

akram	PER	PER

5	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

i.	PER	PER

salisbury	PER	PER

not	O	O

out	O	O

1	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

extras	O	O

(	O	O

lb-11	O	O

w-1	O	O

nb-8	O	O

)	O	O

20	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

total	O	O

(	O	O

for	O	O

six	O	O

wickets	O	O

)	O	O

278	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

fall	O	O

of	O	O

wickets	O	O

:	O	O

1-64	O	ORG

2-85	O	O

3-116	O	O

4-205	O	O

5-248	O	O

6-273	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

to	O	O

bat	O	O

:	O	O

r.	PER	PER

croft	PER	PER

,	O	O

d.	PER	PER

cork	PER	PER

,	O	O

a.	PER	PER

mullally	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

to	O	O

date	O	O

)	O	O

:	O	O

wasim	PER	PER

akram	PER	PER

25-8-61-1	O	O

,	O	O

waqar	PER	PER

younis	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

20-6-70-2	O	ORG

,	O	O

mohammad	PER	PER

akram	PER	PER

12-1-41-1	O	O

,	O	O

mushtaq	PER	PER

ahmed	PER	PER

27-5-78-2	O	O

,	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

aamir	PER	PER

sohail	PER	PER

6-1-17-0	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

:	O	O

aamir	PER	PER

sohail	PER	PER

,	O	O

saeed	PER	PER

anwar	PER	PER

,	O	O

ijaz	PER	PER

ahmed	PER	PER

,	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

salim	PER	PER

malik	PER	PER

,	O	O

asif	PER	PER

mujtaba	PER	PER

,	O	O

wasim	PER	PER

akram	PER	PER

,	O	O

moin	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

khan	PER	LOC

,	O	O

ahmed	PER	PER

,	O	O

waqar	PER	PER

younis	PER	PER

,	O	O

mohammad	PER	PER

akam	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

back	O	O

in	O	O

scottish	MISC	MISC

squad	O	O

after	O	O

20	O	O

months	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

glasgow	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

scored	O	O

united	ORG	ORG

on	O	O

,	O	O

on	O	O

the	O	O

scottish	MISC	MISC

squad	O	O

after	O	O

a	O	O

20-month	O	O

exile	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

glasgow	ORG	LOC

,	O	O

in	O	O

days	O	O

,	O	O

was	O	O

also	O	O

named	O	O

the	O	O

31	O	O

cup	MISC	MISC

qualifier	O	O

against	O	O

austria	LOC	LOC

in	O	O

vienna	LOC	LOC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

,	O	O

who	O	O

in	O	O

in	O	O

1995	O	O

,	O	O

won	O	O

last	O	O

of	O	O

his	O	O

five	O	O

scotland	LOC	LOC

caps	O	O

in	O	O

december	O	O

1994	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

on	O	O

:	O	O

"	O	O

i	O	O

've	O	O

ferguson	PER	PER

twice	O	O

recently	O	O

and	O	O

he	O	O

's	O	O

bang	O	O

in	O	O

form	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

mccoist	PER	PER

is	O	O

also	O	O

in	O	O

great	O	O

scoring	O	O

form	O	O

at	O	O

the	O	O

moment	O	O

.	O	O

"	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

's	O	O

,	O	O

well	O	O

's	O	O

under-21	O	O

,	O	O

earns	O	O

a	O	O

call-up	O	O

to	O	O

the	O	O

senior	O	O

squad	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

cricket	O	O

-	O	O

england	LOC	LOC

100-2	O	O

at	O	O

lunch	O	O

on	O	O

first	O	O

day	O	O

of	O	O

third	O	O

test	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

were	O	O

100	O	O

for	O	O

two	O	O

at	O	O

on	O	O

the	O	O

of	O	O

and	O	O

final	O	O

against	O	O

pakistan	LOC	LOC

at	O	O

the	LOC	LOC

oval	LOC	LOC

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

contract	O	O

with	O	O

manchester	LOC	ORG

united	LOC	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

london	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

roy	PER	PER

keane	PER	PER

has	O	O

a	O	O

new	O	O

with	O	O

english	MISC	MISC

and	O	O

f.a.	MISC	MISC

cup	MISC	MISC

champions	O	O

manchester	ORG	ORG

united	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

"	O	O

roy	PER	PER

a	O	O

deal	O	O

night	O	O

game	O	O

and	O	O

,	O	O

"	O	O

said	O	O

united	ORG	O

manager	O	O

alex	PER	PER

ferguson	PER	PER

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

tennis	O	O

-	O	O

results	O	O

at	O	O

canadian	MISC	MISC

open	MISC	MISC

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

toronto	LOC	LOC

1996-08-21	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

results	O	O

from	O	O

the	O	O

canadian	MISC	MISC

open	MISC	MISC

</s>	O	O

on	O	O

wednesday	O	O

(	O	O

prefix	O	O

number	O	O

denotes	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

seeding	O	O

)	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

second	O	O

round	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

canada	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

1	O	O

-	O	O

thomas	PER	PER

muster	PER	PER

(	O	O

austria	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-3	O	O

7-5	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

)	O	O

beat	O	O

2	O	O

-	O	O

goran	PER	PER

ivanisevic	PER	PER

(	O	O

croatia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

6-7	O	O

(	O	O

3-7	O	O

)	O	O

6-4	O	O

6-4	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

3	O	O

-	O	O

(	O	O

south	LOC	LOC

africa	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

jiri	PER	PER

novak	PER	PER

(	O	O

czech	LOC	LOC

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

republic	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

7-5	O	O

6-3	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

4	O	O

-	O	O

(	O	O

chile	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

kenneth	PER	PER

carlsen	PER	PER

(	O	O

denmark	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-3	O	O

6-2	O	O

</s>	O	O

6	O	O

-	O	O

malivai	PER	PER

(	O	O

u.s.	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

alex	PER	PER

corretja	PER	PER

(	O	O

spain	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-4	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

6-2	O	O

</s>	O	O

7	O	O

-	O	O

todd	PER	PER

martin	PER	PER

(	O	O

u.s.	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

renzo	PER	PER

furlan	PER	PER

(	O	O

italy	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

7-6	O	O

(	O	O

7-3	O	O

)	O	O

6-3	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

australia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

8	O	O

-	O	O

marc	PER	PER

rosset	PER	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

switzerland	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-3	O	O

3-6	O	O

7-6	O	O

(	O	O

8-6	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

9	O	O

-	O	O

(	O	O

france	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

gregory	PER	PER

carraz	PER	PER

(	O	O

france	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

7-6	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

7-1	O	O

)	O	O

6-4	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

)	O	O

beat	O	O

11	O	O

-	O	O

alberto	PER	PER

berasategui	PER	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

spain	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-1	O	O

6-2	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

petr	PER	PER

korda	PER	PER

(	O	O

republic	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

12	O	O

-	O	O

francisco	PER	PER

clavet	PER	PER

(	O	O

spain	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

6-3	O	O

6-4	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

republic	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

13	O	O

-	O	O

jason	PER	PER

stoltenberg	PER	PER

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

australia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

5-7	O	O

7-6	O	O

(	O	O

7-1	O	O

)	O	O

7-6	O	O

(	O	O

13-11	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

todd	PER	PER

woodbridge	PER	PER

(	O	O

beat	O	O

sebastien	PER	PER

lareau	PER	PER

(	O	O

canada	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

6-3	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

1-6	O	O

6-3	O	O

</s>	O	O

alex	PER	PER

o'brien	PER	PER

(	O	O

u.s.	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

byron	PER	PER

black	PER	PER

(	O	O

zimbabwe	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

7-6	O	O

(	O	O

7-2	O	O

)	O	O

6-2	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

republic	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

andrea	PER	PER

gaudenzi	PER	PER

(	O	O

italy	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

6-3	O	O

4-6	O	O

6-1	O	O

</s>	O	O

(	O	O

britain	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

beat	O	O

chris	PER	PER

woodruff	PER	PER

(	O	O

u.s.	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

,	O	O

walkover	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

cricket	O	O

-	O	O

millns	PER	PER

signs	O	O

for	O	O

boland	ORG	ORG

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

cape	LOC	LOC

town	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

boland	ORG	ORG

on	O	O

signed	O	O

fast	O	O

david	PER	PER

millns	PER	PER

on	O	O

a	O	O

one	O	O

year	O	O

contract	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

millns	MISC	ORG

,	O	O

with	O	O

england	LOC	LOC

a	O	O

1992/93	O	O

,	O	O

former	O	O

as	O	O

boland	ORG	ORG

's	O	O

overseas	O	O

professional	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-docstart-	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

-	O	O

european	MISC	MISC

cup	MISC	MISC

winners	MISC	O

'	MISC	MISC

cup	MISC	MISC

results	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

tirana	LOC	LOC

1996-08-22	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

results	O	O

of	O	O

european	MISC	MISC

cup	MISC	MISC

winners	MISC	O

'	MISC	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

cup	MISC	MISC

,	O	O

leg	O	O

soccer	O	O

matches	O	O

on	O	O

thursday	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

tirana	LOC	LOC

:	O	O

vlore	ORG	O

(	O	O

albania	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

0	O	O

chemlon	ORG	O

humenne	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

slovakia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

2	O	O

(	O	O

halftime	O	O

0-0	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scorers	O	O

:	O	O

lubarskij	PER	PER

(	O	O

50th	O	O

minute	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

valkucak	PER	PER

(	O	O

54th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

5,000	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

chemlon	ORG	ORG

humenne	ORG	ORG

win	O	O

3-0	O	O

on	O	O

aggregate	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

in	O	O

:	O	O

gloria	ORG	ORG

bistrita	ORG	ORG

(	O	O

romania	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

2	O	O

valletta	LOC	LOC

(	O	O

malta	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

1	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

1-1	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scorers	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

gloria	ORG	ORG

-	O	O

ilie	PER	PER

lazar	PER	PER

(	O	O

32nd	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

eugen	PER	PER

voica	PER	PER

(	O	O

84th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

valletta	LOC	LOC

-	O	O

gilbert	PER	PER

agius	PER	PER

(	O	O

24th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

8,000	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

gloria	ORG	ORG

bistrita	ORG	ORG

win	O	O

4-2	O	O

on	O	O

aggregate	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

:	O	O

chorzow	ORG	O

(	O	O

poland	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

5	O	O

llansantffraid	ORG	O

(	O	O

wales	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

0	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

1-0	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scorers	O	O

:	O	O

arkadiusz	PER	PER

bak	PER	PER

(	O	O

1st	O	O

and	O	O

55th	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

arwel	PER	PER

jones	PER	PER

(	O	O

47th	O	O

,	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

own	O	O

goal	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

miroslav	PER	PER

bak	PER	PER

(	O	O

62nd	O	O

and	O	O

63rd	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

6,500	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

ruch	ORG	ORG

chorzow	ORG	ORG

win	O	O

6-1	O	O

on	O	O

aggregate	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

:	O	O

(	O	O

cyprus	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

5	O	O

kotaik	ORG	O

abovyan	ORG	O

(	O	O

armenia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

0	O	PER

(	O	O

2-0	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scorers	O	O

:	O	O

zoran	PER	PER

kundic	PER	PER

(	O	O

28th	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

klimis	PER	PER

alexandrou	PER	O

(	O	O

41st	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

</s>	O	O

kovasevic	PER	O

(	O	O

60th	O	O

,	O	O

penalty	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

goran	PER	PER

koprinovic	PER	PER

(	O	O

82nd	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

pavlos	PER	PER

markou	PER	PER

(	O	O

84th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

5,000	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

aek	ORG	ORG

larnaca	ORG	ORG

win	O	O

5-1	O	O

on	O	O

aggregate	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

in	O	O

:	O	O

kareda	ORG	ORG

siauliai	ORG	O

(	O	O

lithuania	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

0	O	O

sion	ORG	ORG

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

switzerland	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

0	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

5,000	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

sion	ORG	ORG

win	O	O

4-2	O	O

on	O	O

agrregate	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

in	O	O

vinnytsya	LOC	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

nyva	ORG	ORG

vinnytsya	ORG	O

(	O	O

ukraine	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

1	O	O

tallinna	ORG	O

sadam	ORG	O

(	O	O

estonia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

0	O	O

(	O	O

0-0	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

3,000	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

aggregate	O	O

score	O	O

2-2	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

nyva	ORG	ORG

qualified	O	O

on	O	O

away	O	O

goals	O	O

rule	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

in	O	O

:	O	O

brann	ORG	ORG

(	O	O

norway	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

2	O	O

shelbourne	ORG	ORG

(	O	O

ireland	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

1	O	O

(	O	O

1-1	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scorers	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

brann	ORG	ORG

-	O	O

ivar	PER	PER

mjelde	PER	PER

(	O	O

10th	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

jan	PER	PER

ove	PER	PER

pedersen	PER	PER

(	O	O

72nd	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

shelbourne	ORG	ORG

-	O	O

mark	PER	PER

rutherford	PER	PER

(	O	O

5th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

2,189	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

brann	ORG	ORG

win	O	O

5-2	O	O

on	O	O

aggregate	O	O

</s>	O	O

in	O	O

:	O	O

sofia	ORG	LOC

(	O	O

bulgaria	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

1	O	O

olimpija	ORG	ORG

(	O	O

slovenia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

0	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

0-0	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scorer	O	O

:	O	O

ilian	PER	ORG

simeonov	PER	O

(	O	O

58th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

25,000	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

aggregate	O	O

1-1	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

olimpija	ORG	ORG

won	O	O

4-3	O	O

on	O	O

penalties	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

in	O	O

:	O	O

vaduz	LOC	LOC

(	O	O

liechtenstein	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

1	O	O

raf	ORG	ORG

riga	ORG	ORG

(	O	O

latvia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

1	O	O

(	O	O

0-0	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scorers	O	O

:	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

vaduz	LOC	LOC

-	O	O

daniele	PER	PER

polverino	PER	PER

(	O	O

90th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

raf	ORG	ORG

riga	ORG	ORG

-	O	O

agrins	PER	O

zarins	PER	O

(	O	O

47th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

aggregate	O	O

2-2	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

vaduz	LOC	LOC

won	O	O

4-2	O	O

on	O	O

penalties	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

:	O	O

us	ORG	LOC

luxembourg	ORG	LOC

(	O	O

luxembourg	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

0	O	O

varteks	ORG	O

varazdin	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

(	O	O

croatia	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

3	O	O

(	O	O

0-0	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

scorers	O	O

:	O	O

beser	PER	O

(	O	O

63rd	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

miljenko	PER	PER

mumler	PER	O

(	O	O

penalty	O	O

,	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

78th	O	O

)	O	O

,	O	O

jamir	PER	PER

cvetko	PER	O

(	O	O

87th	O	O

)	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

attendance	O	O

:	O	O

800	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

varteks	ORG	ORG

varazdin	ORG	ORG

win	O	O

5-1	O	O

on	O	O

aggregate	O	O

.	O	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O

:	O	O

boltfelag	ORG	O

(	O	O

faroe	LOC	LOC

islands	LOC	LOC

)	O	O

0	O	O

dynamo	ORG	O

</s>	O	O

<s>	O	O
